Oh, the way you crushed
Mike at Ping-Pong
was such a turn-on.
You want to...?
You know, I'd love to,
but I'm a little tired.
I'll put a pillowcase
over my head.
You're on.
Hey.
What's up?
Well, okay, Mike's
taking a shower,
which, by the way,
there's no law against.
And then we're going
to grab some food.
So, if you want...
( door closing )
ROSS:
Finally we have
some privacy.
Is that Ross?
Yeah, you can hear
everything
through these
stupid walls.
...just wanted
to kiss you...
Sounds like
he's with someone.
He could be alone.
This morning I heard
him do push-ups
and then talk
to his triceps.
Wait a minute,
I think Phoebe's right.
Yeah, I hear someone else
in there with him.
( moaning )
Dr. Geller.
God, you're amazing.
I didn't even have to ask you
to call me that.
Oh, my God.
That's Charlie.
She's cheating on Joey
with Ross.
Oh, that tart,
floozy... giant.
I'm not sure about this.
Yeah, you're right;
this is none of our business.
No, I'm not sure
that was the best way
to hear everything.
Someone get me a glass.
No, I'm not going
to do this, okay?
I'm not going to eavesdrop
on my friend.
RACHEL:
Oh, Joe, I am really starting
to love Barbados.
( both moaning softly )
I can't believe
I'm kissing you.
I'm kissing Rachel!
I know. I'm her.
Rachel and Joey--
it's Rachel and Joey!
What?!
Get over here!
RACHEL:
Ah.
Whoa.
Oh, my God.
I love how thin
these walls are!
Thank you.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, you know,
before you said
that nothing could
happen between us.
What changed?
Well, I only said that
because of Ross.
Mm.
You know, then I saw him
kissing Charlie...
What?
Ross and Charlie?
Wow, she's really
making her way
through the group, huh?
Eh, who am I to talk?
I can't believe this.
Rachel and Joey?
How about the dinosaur
twins in the other room?
No one is manning
that wall.
I'm on it.
Anything?
I think I hear
curtains closing.
We've got shoes being kicked off
over here.
Bedsprings... unmistakable.
You do realize
that's your brother?
Not until you said it.
Somebody switch!
Wow.
Wait a minute.
Ross and Charlie,
Joey and Rachel,
Phoebe and Mike.
We're the only people leaving
with the same person
we came with.
That's not true.
I came with Monica,
and I'm leaving with Weird Al.
Okay, I've had it
with the hair jokes.
Tomorrow morning, before we
leave, I'm going to the salon.
Okay, Buckwheat.
( exasperated sigh )
You-you got to hear this.
It's great.
It's like, it's like free porn.
Wa...
Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's just I-I don't
think I can do this.
Oh...
Is it because of what
might be on the bedspread,
'cause I saw that
news report too
with the infrared,
and we could just...
No, no.
No, uh...
Look, I-I need
to talk to Joey.
I mean, you guys
just broke up.
Before anything more
happens between us,
I need to know
he's okay with it.
I, uh... I completely
understand.
All right, I'm going
to go find him.
I just need a second
before I can... you know.
Grandma, Grandma, Grandma...
Okay, I'll see you later.
Okay.
( door closes )
That's the door.
He's gone.
And she's turning
on the TV,
and watching...
Miss Congeniality.
Honey, if you know it
through a wall,
you know it too well.
Hey, what are
you guys doing?
Oh, we're just...
we're sad to go,
so we're just saying
good-bye to the hotel.
I love you....
Paradise hotel,
golf resort and spa.
Yep, we had
a great time.
Thank you.
Bye.
Okay.
Um, hey, have you guys
seen Joey anywhere?
He's probably in his room
with his current
girlfriend Charlie.
That's the situation
as we know it.
Well, if you see him,
can you please tell him
I'm looking for him?
You got it.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Other wall, people,
other wall.
( knocking )
Rach, you there?
Oh, my God.
That's Ross.
What are we
going to do?
Okay, just be calm,
just be calm.
For all he knows
we're just...
we're just
hanging out together.
All right, so just
be nonchalant.
That's not nonchalant.
I have no idea what it means.
Oh!
Okay, just hide.
( knocking )
Rach?
Coming.
Try under the bed,
try under the bed.
There's no room
under the bed.
Is everything
okay?
Yeah.
Hey.
Hi.
Do you know where
Joey is?
I really don't.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Yeah, sure.
I don't believe this.
Have you guys been...?
Shh. This is the
listening side of the wall.
And then she told me that
she and Joey had broken up,
and that part
of the reason
was that she had
feelings for me.
Uh-huh, right. Yeah.
And you know I've wanted
to ask Charlie out
since the day I met her.
I know, I know.
It's been really
hard for you.
Anyway, one thing
led to another, and...
before you know it,
we were kissing.
How angry do you think
Joey's going to be?
That is hard to say, Ross.
That's hard to say.
You know, I got
to go find him.
He's got to be here someplace.
You would think.
Joey?
JOEY:
Is he gone?
How are you doing this?!
Psst.
Hey. What are you...?
What is this?
Have you guys been
listening this entire time?
Yeah.
Now, what is this?
What is this?
Well, let's see...
we kissed for ten minutes
and now we're talking
to our friends about it,
so I guess this
is sixth grade.
No, no.
Have you thought about
how complicated
this could get?
What about Ross?
Look, he's
with Charlie now.
Yeah, but he wants
to talk to you
before anything
really happens with her.
And as his friend, I mean,
don't you think
he deserves
the same from you?
You're a pain
in my ass, Geller.
All right, look, you guys,
look, we appreciate
all the advice,
but this is between
Joey and me
and I think
we can handle it.
Okay, we'll
go back in there,
but will you do
one thing for us--
the people that
care about you?
Sure.
Enunciate.
( distinctly ):
Get out.
Are they right?
Probably, yeah.
I mean, maybe we should...
hold off until we talk to Ross.
Yeah.
Yeah. It can wait.
We don't have to do
anything tonight.
Yeah, I-I think that'd be best.
So... so...
I'm going to...
I'm going to take off.
Although...
I like although.
I mean, you know...
Ross and I haven't
dated in like...
six years.
Six years?
Wow. That's almost
as long as high school.
Plus, you know,
he is with Charlie now.
Absolutely.
He's not thinking
about you.
No.
I'm thinking about you.
Yeah.
Let's forget about Ross.
It's forgotten.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
( Joey's voice ):
Seriously, what is it?
Nothing. It's really...
it's nothing.
Come here, come here.
What's wrong?
Sorry, I just, um...
I can't seem to get
Ross out of my head.
Well, maybe I can help.
( Rachel's voice ):
Ah, your lips are so soft.
Do that again.
( gasping )
Yeah, we... we...
we need to talk to Ross.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey.
You guys ready to go?
Not quite.
Monica's still at the salon,
and I'm just finishing packing.
Dude, you're not
taking your Bible?
You're not supposed
to take that.
Besides, it's a New Testament.
What are you gonna do with it?
Learn about Jesus.
Hey.
So, did you talk to Joey?
Uh, no, no.
I couldn't find him.
Uh, I'm just gonna talk
to him on the plane.
Okay.
Sounds like a good idea...
Dr. Geller.
Stop it.
Ph.D...
You're filthy.
Hey, have you
guys seen Monica?
Uh, actually, I think
she went to the salon.
Oh, yeah. Oh, she went
to the salon, all right.
Check it out!
Whose day just got better?
Chandler!
Hey...
Ah...!
What do you think?
I think...
I think I can see your scalp.
Don't you just love it?
Y-Yeah, yeah.
Y-You got shellfish
in your head.
It's, uh... it's something.
You go, girlfriend!
You've never said that
in your life, have you?
Not once.
I thought so.
Oh! And listen to this.
( shells rattling )
What do you know?
It's a treat for the eyes
and the ears.
Ooh!
Wow, it's, uh...
kind of weird.
I'm sitting next to
Charlie after we broke up.
Yeah, it's almost
as if Air Barbados
doesn't care
about your social life.
Hey, look, does
someone mind switching
and sitting with Charlie?
Oh, I mean, I...
Dude, I spent
the whole conference
with Charlie.
I understand.
No, I'll do it.
Wish I could switch
with someone.
I really don't want to sit
with Allen Iverson over there.
Um, you know,
once we're in the air,
and the captain turns off
the seat-belt sign,
you feel free
to roam about my cabin.
You should be careful
when checking
your overhead bins...
'cause items may shift during...
Aw, you're not good at this.
Hey, you don't have to go home
tonight, do you?
No, I think I could come over.
It's Saturday, right?
Oh...
What?
Um, I can't do
anything tonight.
Why not?
I have a date.
You have a...
You have a date?
With who?
Oh, it's...
my girlfriend.
You have...
you have a
girlfriend?
Yeah.
Well, when you and I broke up,
I started seeing someone.
Well, for how long?
Three months.
Three months?
Okay.
This is probably
none of my business,
but how long do you think
you're gonna keep seeing her?
I'll tell her that it's over
tonight at dinner.
I promise.
Oh, okay, good.
You do that.
And then when you get home,
maybe there'll be
a special delivery package
waiting for you.
Then maybe I'll sign for it...
tear it open...
pull out
the packing material...
You know what?
We're gonna have sex.
Let's just leave it there.
All right.
I'm gonna go
talk to Joey.
I think this is
the right time.
He's always in
a good mood
after the flight
attendant says
"duty-free."
Okay.
Good luck.
Ross is coming over.
I think now would be a really
good time to talk to him.
Well, I guess so.
I'm just... really nervous.
Okay, well, keep in mind
that by the time you're done,
they'll probably
be serving dinner.
Ooh.
Still nervous?
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
Hey, Rach?
Yeah?
Do you mind if I
sit here for a sec?
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, sure!
Yeah.
( sighs )
Hey.
So, I, um...
I kinda need to talk
to you about Charlie.
Yeah?
Okay, last night,
after you guys broke up--
so sorry to hear
about that, by the way--
well, Charlie and I
were talking, and...
Well...
You kissed?
( sputtering laugh )
What?!
Wha-Wha-What would
give you that idea?
I saw you.
Yeah, we kissed.
But... nothing else,
nothing else
happened, okay?
Ross, Ross...
It's okay.
What?
Look, I totally understand,
all right?
You guys make way more sense
than her and I ever did,
you know, and...
I want you to be happy.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Now, I have something...
I am speechless.
I mean, the fact
that you would put my
happiness first like that?
I mean, you-you...
you're an incredible
friend, you know that?
Well, look, before you go...
No, I-I mean it.
I mean, you are so...
you're so loyal,
man, and-and selfless
and generous.
I am those things, yeah.
You know, I've known
Chandler longer,
so I always think of
him as my best friend.
But now...
I'm gonna have to
rethink some stuff.
Oh, dude!
Hey, if there is ever
anything I can do for you...
I can't think of anything.
ROSS:
Thanks.
Yeah.
So, hi.
Hi.
So, you, uh, so,
you talked to Joey?
Oh, yeah.
We had a really good talk.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
Oh, so, everything's okay?
Oh, no, it's great.
It's great.
He's an amazing guy.
Ah, well, obviously,
I think so, too.
Well, I am
so excited about this.
Really?
Excited?
Are you kidding?
I have had some very
dirty dreams about this.
Excuse me.
You didn't tell
him, did you?
I couldn't.
He was saying all these
really nice things about me.
I didn't want him to get mad
and take them all back.
I'm gonna edge out Chandler.
Oh, God!
All right, fine.
You know what, Joey?
Forget it. When we
go back to New York,
I will tell him.
Thank you.
Yeah, I appreciate that.
Ha-ha-ha-ho-ho!
Ho-ho...
( phone ringing )
Hi, Mike's place.
Hey, it's Mike.
Ooh, that was fast.
Oh, no, she's not here yet.
You know, I think
I'm just going to take off
and break up with her
over the phone.
You can't do that.
Oh, come on, Mike,
strap on a pair.
Why don't you just tell her
that we got back together?
You know, women
appreciate honesty.
We also appreciate a gentle
spanking once in a while,
just FYI.
Oh, um...
one more thing.
There might be a picture
of Precious on my coffee table.
Her name's Precious?
Is she a purebreed, or did you
pick her up at the pound?
Anyway, I just wanted
to give you a heads up.
Okay... Oh, and you know,
if she gets upset,
just scratch her tummy
and give her a Liva Snap.
( laughs )
( knocking at door )
Hi, I'm Precious.
Who are you?
I'm-I'm Phoebe.
Phoebe?
Mike's ex-girlfriend
The love of his life?
That Phoebe?
Enchantée.
Oh, I can't wait for
everyone at work to see these.
Ow!
You go back to work
tomorrow night, right?
Yeah.
So, if you want people
to see them,
then by definition you're
not having them taken out,
say at that break of dawn?
Well, if I had them
taken out,
then I wouldn't
be able to do this.
( groans )
You like that,
right?
( humming )
What are you singing?
It's "Bolero," from Ten.
It's "Ride of the Valkyries"
from Apocalypse Now.
See, here's the thing.
The corn rows
were really a solution
to your frizzy hair problem,
and now that we're home
you don't have
that problem anymore.
So if you think about it,
I hate them.
What?
You said you liked them.
Did I?
Let's refresh.
I believe what I said was
that I could see your scalp.
Well, fine, so you
don't like them.
Everybody else does.
Again,
let's journey back.
As I recall,
what Rachel said was,
she had never noticed
the shape
of your skull before.
And Joey...
Well, Joey didn't realize
there was anything different.
Well, you know what,
I don't care.
I like it like this
and I'm going to keep it.
You're just jealous because
your hair can't do this.
Ow!
Get yourself in the tooth?
And the eye.
( knocking at door )
( gasping )
BOTH:
Hi.
There she is.
Hi, Emma.
Oh, my God, I missed you.
Oh, Emma, I missed you so much.
Hi.
Did you have a good time
with Grandma Green, huh?
Did she give you a bottle
of antidepressants again
to use as a rattle?
That was one time, Ross,
and they were only, like,
five milligrams.
Ooh, hey, Emma, Daddy
has some presents for you.
Okay, okay, I want you
to wait right here.
Come here, sweetie.
Ross, um, actually there's
something that, uh,
I really need to talk
to you about.
Okay, shoot.
Okay.
Um, all right, here's the deal.
Oh, no!
What, what is it?
Oh, major shampoo explosion.
All right, look.
Uh, look, Ross,
this really isn't easy.
Oh, it's all over everything!
Why? Why me?
Because you took
300 bottles of shampoo?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You were saying?
Well, yeah, okay, look.
It's about me and...
Oh, not another one!
Oh, my... and this moisturizer.
It's even harder to clean!
Why? Why do bad things
happen to good people?
Wow.
Well, clearly
this is not a good time.
Uh, you think?!
Okay, bye.
All right, so Mike's
on his way over.
See, you thought you guys
were meeting here
and he thought you were meeting
at the restaurant, so, you know,
doesn't really matter
who's right or wrong.
The point is...
I'm going to take off.
Wait, no.
I'm not letting you leave
until you tell me
what's going on here.
I mean, are you guys getting
back together or something?
All right.
Susie...
can I call you Susie?
My name is Precious.
I can't say that.
Um, Susie, I'm going to be
straight with you.
Mike and I are back together,
and, um, unfortunately
that effectively ends
your relationship
with him,
and he's very sorry about that
and wishes you the best of luck
in all your endeavors.
I just can't believe this.
Why?
Well, I don't...
Why would
he do this?
I mean, what's
wrong with me?
Nothing, there's
nothing wrong with you.
I mean, what the hell
am I supposed to do now?
Damn it, woman, pull
yourself together.
Have some pride,
for the love of God!
( crying )
Okay, not a fan
of the tough love.
I just can't believe
that Mike didn't
give me any warning.
But he didn't really
know, you know?
He wasn't planning
on coming to Barbados
and proposing to me.
He proposed to you?
This is the worst birthday ever.
Look... Precious.
Mike's not worth this.
You're an attractive,
intelligent woman,
and let's face it,
Mike's kind of a wang.
And he proposed
to me while he was
still seeing you.
He was going to break up
with you on your birthday?
And-- I don't like
to kiss and tell--
but he cheated on you
a lot this weekend.
Oh, my God, you know,
maybe you're right.
Maybe I don't need him.
I deserve to be treated
with respect.
Screw you, Mike.
You're a coward
and a bastard,
and I hope
you rot in hell.
You're welcome.
Honey, you've been in there
for a long time.
Is everything okay?
Not really.
I have a problem.
Really?
What happened?
Well, I was dancing around
and singing "No Woman, No Cry,"
and, uh... I got stuck.
You can't move
at all?
Oh, I can move.
If I untangle you, will you
please get rid of the corn rows?
I guess so.
Some of these
look a little frayed.
Yeah, I tried
to gnaw myself free.
Hey.
Hi.
So, did you, uh,
did you tell Ross?
Well, I tried,
but then he had
a shampoo-related emergency.
So I guess
now it's your turn again.
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
I think it's better if
you tell him, you know?
And it's easier
for a woman.
That way if he gets mad,
all you have to do is go,
"I didn't mean it.
I'm so sorry."
Yeah, 'cause that's what we do.
All right,
all right, okay.
Um, how about this,
how about this.
Tomorrow...
Mm-hmm.
Tomorrow we'll both go
and we'll tell him together.
Okay,
that sounds fair.
That just means
though...
I know, I know.
But that's okay.
I mean, we can
control ourselves.
We're not animals.
( scoffs ):
No.
Of course,
we can wait.
All right, so I guess
that means good night then.
Yep. Good night.
Good night.
Seriously, good night.
Stop saying good night.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
Look what I found in the drawer.
And you said I'd
never wear this.
Now that I untangled you,
how about you do
a little something for me?
Sure. What do you have in mind?
I think you know.
Really?
I don't really
feel like it.
This is what I want to do.
Okay.
I just don't get why
you like it so much.
She's an FBI agent
posing as a beauty contestant.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org